premiumwebcart.com 2010-03-13

# PremiumWebCart.com - A Complete Marketing Solution

This Privacy Policy governs our policies and practices regarding the collection, use, and disclosure of your personal information that is disclosed via our websites.

##### 1\. Personal Information

Personal Information includes your name, address, e-mail address, and phone number, as well as other non-public information that is associated with the foregoing ("Personal Information"). Personal Information may be processed by PremiumWebCart.com, Developer(s), or User(s) in the country where it was collected, as well as other countries (including the United States) where laws regarding processing of Personal Information may be less stringent.

The collection of Personal Information helps us learn about our customers and potential customers. This information may be used to contact you with information and offers regarding our products and services.

Other information may also be collected via our websites, such as your Internet Protocol address, browser type, and operating system. We use cookies and navigational data to gather information regarding the date and time of your visit and information that you have searched and/or viewed.

##### 2\. Consent

By submitting Personal Information, you agree to the terms of this Policy and expressly consent to the processing of Personal Information in accordance with this Policy.

##### 3\. Use of Personal Information

PremiumWebCart.com may process and store Personal Information on behalf of our customers that have been posted on our websites from the users of such websites. PremiumWebCart.com does not own the Personal Information, and we will only use Personal Information appropriately. The Personal Information you submit to us is used either to set up solutions or purchase website marketing services, respond to requests that you make, to process transactions, to facilitate your request for a quote from a third party service provider or to aid us in serving you better. We may also use your Personal Information to provide you with electronic newsletters or promotional e-mails as well as information and offers about our products and services.

##### 4\. Disclosure of Personal Information

Except as otherwise stated in this Privacy Policy, we do not generally share Personal Information with third parties, and we will not disclose any confidential or financial information unless requested by you. We may engage third parties to assist us, and, in connection with such assistance, we may provide them with Personal Information as necessary. To drive traffic to your website and to make your website easier to find, we will disclose keywords about your business, your business name, general and specific description about your business, including information about your products and services, to third-party services and the general public.

We currently have subsidiaries and other companies under a common control (collectively, "affiliates"). We may share some or all of your Personal Information with these affiliates, and we will require our affiliates to honor this Privacy Policy. Further, if our company or our assets are acquired by another company, that company will possess the Personal Information collected by us and will assume the rights and obligations regarding your Personal Information as described in this Policy.

We may also disclose your Personal Information if we believe in good faith that such disclosure is necessary to (a) comply with relevant laws or to respond to subpoenas or warrants served on PremiumWebCart.com; or (b) to protect and defend the rights or property of PremiumWebCart.com or users of our website or our customers' websites.

We also use third parties to maintain and store your Personal Information and to process any payment you make to us. Generally, these third parties are required not to use your Personal Information other than to provide the services requested by PremiumWebCart.com.

##### 5\. Opt-Out Opportunity

Should you decide to stop receiving further communications or newsletters from us, you will have the opportunity to "opt-out" by following the unsubscribe instructions provided in the e-mail. If at any time you wish to subscribe to any communications from us, you may do so by contacting us at support@PremiumWebCart.com . Despite your indicated e-mail preferences, we may send you notices of any updates of our legal policies to the account you created with us.

##### 6\. External Websites

Any links to external websites are for convenience purposes only, and do not signify any endorsement or affiliation with our website. We do not control the content on external websites, we do not review that content, and we cannot be held responsible for that content. The terms in this Policy are not applicable to external websites.

##### 7\. Security Measures

We will use reasonable measures to maintain the security of your Personal Information. However, technical mistakes may be possible, as no company can fully eliminate security risks associated with Personal Information.

##### 8\. Dispute Resolution

If you choose to visit PremiumWebCart.com's website, your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Privacy Policy, as governed by the laws of the State of Illinois.

##### 9\. Minors

Our website is not designed for minors under the age of 18. We do not intentionally gather Personal Information about visitors under the age of 18.

##### 10\. Privacy Policy Updates

This Privacy Policy is subject to revision, and if we make any substantial changes in the way we use your Personal Information, we will post an alert on this page. If you object to any such changes, you must cease using our website. Continued use of our website following notice of any such changes shall indicate your acknowledgment of such changes and agreement to be bound by the terms and conditions of such changes.

This statement was last updated on July 15, 2009.

##### 11\. Contact Us

Should you have any questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact us:  

PremiumWebCart.com  
Privacy Officer  
1740 H Dell Range Blvd Suite, 281  
Cheyenne, WY 82009
